Guide to the Intercollegiate Center for Nursing Education Director (Hilda Boerhave Roberts) Papers 1924-2001
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Intercollegiate Center for Nursing Education (ICNE)--Faculty Organizations, Series 3A
  - ICNE Faculty Meeting--Correspondence and Schedules - 1969 to 1973 (Folder 11)
  - ICNE Faculty Meeting--Minutes and Materials - 1969 to 1971 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Faculty Meeting--Minutes and Materials - 1971 to 1974 (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Faculty Organization Council Correspondence - 1974 to 1982 (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Faculty Organization Council, Minutes and Materials - 1973 to 1983 (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Historical Committee Agenda and Minutes - 1980 to 1981 (Folder 5)
  - ICNE Interinstitutional Committee on Nursing--Correspondence and Materials - 1967 to 1972 (Folder 6)
  - ICNE Interinstitutional Committee on Nursing--Minutes and Reports - 1967 to 1971 (Folder 7)
  - ICNE Interinstitutional Committee on Nursing Education "Meeting of the Presidents" Notes and Materials - 1968 (Folder 8)
  - ICNE Joint Taskforce - 1973 (Folder 9)
  - ICNE Library Committee Minutes and Annual Report - 1970 to 1972 (Folder 10)
  - ICNE Maternal-Child Nursing Faculty Meeting Minutes and Conferences - 1970 to 1972 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Medical-Surgical Nursing Instructors Correspondence and Reports - 1971 (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Medical-Surgical Nursing Instructors Meetings and Conferences - 1970 to 1972 (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Minority Affairs Committee--Campus Visits - 1972 (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Minority Affairs Committee--Correspondence and Materials - 1972 to 1980 (Folder 5)
  - ICNE Minority Affairs Committee--Minutes and Reports - 1972 to 1982 (Folder 6)
  - ICNE Minority Affairs Committee--Notes, Literature, and "You-In" Program Brochures - 1970s to 1980s (Folder 7)
  - ICNE Nominating Committee Annual Reports - 1975 to 1982 (Folder 8)
  - ICNE Nursing Advisors Committee Correspondence - 1969 to 1982 (Folder 9)
  - ICNE Nursing Advisors Committee Meeting Minutes and Annual Reports - 1974 to 1980 (Folder 10)
  - ICNE Personnel Committee Annual Reports - 1972 to 1980 (Folder 11)
  - ICNE RN/BSN Task Force Committee - 1973 (Folder 12)
  - ICNE Research and Grant Committee--Minutes - 1970 to 1971 (Folder 13)
  - ICNE Student-Faculty Affairs Committee--Minutes and Annuals Reports - 1970 to 1982 (Folder 14)
  - WSU Administrative Council Admissions Committee Minutes and Hilda B. Roberts Notes - 1973 (Folder 15)
- Washington State College/Washington State University Nursing Student Life, Series 3B
  - Association of Intercollegiate Nursing Students--Bylaws and Minutes - 1969 to 1971 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Correspondence with Nursing Students - 1968 to 1982 (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Graduation and Student Recognition Ceremonies - 1963 to 1987 (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Handbook for Nursing Students - 1970 to 1974 (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Handbook for Nursing Students - 1974 to 1978 (Folder 5)
  - ICNE Handbook for Nursing Students - 1980 to 1982 (Folder 6)
  - ICNE Nursing Orientation Materials and Hilda B. Roberts Notes - 1969 to 1981 (Folder 7)
  - ICNE Nursing Student Life Photograph Slides of Student Activities - 1970 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Nursing Student Placement and Certification Exam Materials and Correspondence - 1970 to 1982 (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Nursing Student Profiles by Graduating Class - 1970 to 1981 (Folder 3)
  - ICNE National Honors Society of Nursing Delta Chi Chapter - 1980 (Folder 4)
  - Rho Nu and WSC School of Nursing Blood Drives - 1950 to 1956 (Folder 5)
  - Rho Nu Budget and Financial Documents - 1961 to 1981 (Folder 6)
  - Rho Nu Constitution and Bylaws - 1942 to 1975 (Folder 7)
  - Rho Nu Correspondence, General - 1946 to 1981 (Folder 8)
  - Rho Nu Correspondence with Nursing Advisor Hilda Roberts - 1951 to 1982 (Folder 9)
  - Rho Nu Hilda B. Roberts Notes and Materials - 1974 to 1986 (Folder 10)
  - Rho Nu Initiation and General Information - 1946 to 1974 (Folder 11)
  - Rho Nu Membership and Pledge Lists - 1945 to 1982 (Folder 12)
  - Rho Nu Newspaper Articles - 1948 to 1982 (Folder 13)
  - Rho Nu Newsletters "Rho News" - 1973 to 1981 (Folder 14)
  - Rho Nu Officer and Committee Materials - 1946 to 1983 (Folder 15)
  - Rho Nu Officer and Student Body Meetings Minutes - 1942 to 1958 (Folder 16)
  - Rho Nu Photographs - 1945 to 1956 (Folder 17)
  - Rho Nu Minutes of Meetings - 1948 to 1965 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Rho Nu Secretary's Notebook - 1969 to 1970 (Folder 2)
  - Rho Nu Treasurer's Book - 1948 to 1965 (Folder 3)
  - Rho Nu Student Nursing Organization Meeting Minutes - 1969 to 1979 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Rho Nu Treasurer's Report - 1969 to 1971 (Folder 2)
  - Rho Nu Volunteer and Professional Activities - 1952 to 1986 (Folder 3)
  - State of Washington Associated Nursing Students (SWANS) - 1950 to 1982 (Folder 4)
  - WSC and ICNE Nursing Student Alumni Listings - 1908 to 1976 (Folder 5)
  - WSC and ICNE Nursing Student Alumni Reunions and Events - 1956 to 2001 (Folder 6)
  - WSC and ICNE Nursing Student Life Newspaper Articles - 1947 to 1971 (Folder 7)
  - WSC and ICNE Nursing Student Scholarships and Financial Aid - 1941 to 1987 (Folder 8)
  - WSC and ICNE School of Nursing Graduation and Class Photographs - 1944 to 1973 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - WSC and St. Luke's School of Nursing Student Life Photographs "Career Program" at WSC - 1953 to 1955 (Folder 2)
  - WSC and St. Luke's School of Nursing Student Life Photographs "Finch Hall Dormitory" - 1945 to 1955 (Folder 3)
  - WSC and St. Luke's School of Nursing Student Life Photographs "In Library" - 1955 (Folder 4)
  - WSC and St. Luke's School of Nursing Student Life Photographs--Nursing Student Activities - 1950s (Folder 5)
  - WSC and St. Luke's School of Nursing Student Life Photographs "Student Health Program" - 1955 (Folder 6)
  - WSC and St. Luke's School of Nursing Student Life Photographs "Student Uniforms" - 1949 to 1968 (Folder 7)
  - WSC and St. Luke's School of Nursing Student Procedures and Guidelines - 1940s to 1950s (Folder 8)
  - WSC School of Nursing Alumni Correspondence and Newsletters - 1947 to 1959 (Folder 9)
  - WSC School of Nursing Correspondence with Enrolled Nursing Students - 1957 (Folder 10)
  - WSC School of Nursing Graduation and Student Recognition Ceremonies - 1942 to 1955 (Folder 11)
  - WSC School of Nursing Student Achievement Test Median Percentile Scores - 1952 to 1958 (Folder 12)
  - WSC School of Nursing "Student Handbook" - 1950 to 1955 (Folder 13)
  - WSC School of Nursing Student Organization "The Associated Students of Finch Hall" - 1951 to 1956 (Folder 14)
  - WSC Nursing Student Questionnaires and Surveys - 1947 to 1968 (Folder 15)
- Hilda Roberts’ Personal Papers, 1924-1992, Series 4
  - Hilda B. Roberts Activities and Awards Newspaper Articles - 1951 to 1989 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Hilda B. Roberts and Other Nursing Faculty Photographs - 1950s to 1970s (Folder 2)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Application for National League for Nursing Fellowship - 1953 to 1958 (Folder 3)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Biographical Data and Personal Biography - 1952 to 1980 (Folder 4)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Columbia University Teacher's College, New York Admissions Materials and Correspondence - 1950 to 1955 (Folder 5)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Correspondence Drafts and Memos - 1970s to 1980s (Folder 6)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Correspondence Personal - 1951 to 1982 (Folder 7)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Correspondence with "Joint Planning Committee…In Tuberculosis Nursing" Walla Walla, WA, Veterans Administration Hospital - 1949 to 1956 (Folder 8)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Correspondence with the Teachers College at Columbia University - 1952 to 1967 (Folder 9)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Correspondence with University of Washington Nursing Faculty Dean Elizabeth Soule - 1941 to 1953 (Folder 10)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Correspondence with University of Washington Nursing Faculty Dean Mary S. Tschudin - 1950 to 1969 (Folder 11)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Correspondence with University of Washington Nursing Faculty Florence Gray - 1954 to 1973 (Folder 12)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Correspondence with University of Washington Nursing Faculty Various - 1948 to 1989 (Folder 13)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Correspondence with University of Washington Nursing Faculty Virginia Olcott - 1947 to 1964 (Folder 14)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Correspondence with Various Nursing Schools and Organizations - 1950 to 1966 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Correspondence with Washington State Hospitals - 1964 to 1971 (Folder 2)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Course Materials "Industrial Hygiene Course" - 1944 (Folder 3)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Faculty Personnel Record and C.V. - 1941 to 1989 (Folder 4)
  - Hilda B. Roberts ICNE Administration Notebook - 1971 to 1972 (Folder 5)
  - Hilda B. Roberts ICNE Faculty Binder - 1970 to 1971 (Folder 6)
  - Hilda B. Roberts ICNE Faculty Binder - 1971 to 1972 (Folder 7)
  - Hilda B. Roberts ICNE Faculty Binder - 1975 to 1976 (Folder 8)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Interview and Meeting Notes Various Topics - 1960s (Folder 9)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Graduate Coursework "Education 247: Seminar in Guidance" - 1947 (Folder 10)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Graduate Coursework "Education 274" - 1948 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Graduate Coursework Education S520: Seminar in Curriculum and Instruction - 1953 (Folder 2)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Invention "Syringe Tray" Research Materials and Correspondence - 1947 to 1954 (Folder 3)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Lecture "Current Trends in Nursing" - 1962 (Folder 4)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Master's Thesis Research Materials and Draft - 1948 to 1949 (Folder 5)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Notes Administrative - 1960s to 1970s (Folder 6)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Nursing Collection Processing Notes and Materials (Folder 7)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Nursing Conference Notes and Materials - 1975 (Folder 8)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Nursing Conferences at University of Washington - 1949 to 1953 (Folder 9)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Nursing Conferences "National Conference on Women in the Defense Decade" - 1950 to 1951 (Folder 10)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Nursing Courses "Diet and Ward Therapies" - 1938 (Folder 11)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Nursing Courses "Diet Therapy" - 1937 (Folder 12)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Nursing Courses Education 291E "Curriculum Development in Nursing Education" - 1951 to 1952 (Folder 13)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Nursing Courses Education 292J Legal Aspects of Nursing and Nursing Education - 1950s (Folder 14)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Nursing Courses: Nursing Education 76-- "Ear, Nose, Throat, Eye, Teeth Lectures" - 1938 (Folder 15)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Nursing Courses Education 520: Scientific Principles - 1953 (Folder 16)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Nursing Courses "Physiology Drawings 54" - 1936 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Nursing Courses "Surgical Study" - 1938 (Folder 2)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Nursing Notes Various Topics (Folder 3)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Nursing Poetry Collection - 1944 to 1968 (Folder 4)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Nursing Programs Collection Materials on Collegiate Nursing Schools - 1966 to 1967 (Folder 5)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Nursing Programs collection Materials on University of Colorado Program - 1968 to 1973 (Folder 6)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Nursing Programs Collection Materials on Sacred Heart School of Nursing of Gonzaga University - 1944 to 1945 (Folder 7)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Nursing Programs Collection Materials on University of Washington Program - 1940 to 1980 (Folder 8)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Nursing Programs collection Publications and Research in University of Washington Program - 1934 to 1992 (Folder 9)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Nursing Publication Collection Assorted Materials on Nursing Education - 1939 to 1980 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Nursing Publication Collection Assorted Materials on Nursing History - 1924 to 1972 (Folder 2)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Nursing Publication Collection Assorted Materials on the Nursing Life - 1937 to 1970 (Folder 3)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Nursing Publication Collection Assorted Materials on Nursing Research - 1946 to 1989 (Folder 4)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Nursing Publication Collection "Collective Bargaining in the Nursing and Hospital Field" - 1949 to 1951 (Folder 5)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Nursing Publication Collection "Integrated Nursing Science Course in Washington Junior Colleges" - 1956 (Folder 6)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Nursing Publication Collection Materials on Disaster Nursing - 1958 to 1969 (Folder 7)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Nursing Publication Collection Materials on Nursing in the Peace Corps and Vista - 1970s (Folder 8)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Nursing Publication "Nurse Education Program Feasibility Study for Central Washington University, Ellensburg, WA - 1971 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Nursing Publication Collection "Standard Practice Nursing Procedures" - 1936 (Folder 2)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Nursing Publication Collection "The Journal of Nursing Education" - 1969 to 1970 (Folder 3)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Nursing Publication Collection Washington State Schools of Nursing - 1965 to 1980 (Folder 4)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Publication "New Type of Syringe Tray Developed" - 1948 (Folder 5)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Publication "Nursing---Your Career" - 1952 (Folder 6)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Publication "Planning Your Future in Nursing" - 1950 (Folder 7)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Publication "Supervision of the Polio Unit" - 1950 to 1954 (Folder 8)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Publication "The Developing Nursing Technician Program in the Community Colleges" - 1952 (Folder 9)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Reports on School of Nursing in the Modern Community" - 1940s (Folder 10)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Research Notes Various Topics - 1960s (Folder 11)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Retirement Materials and Correspondence - 1982 to 1983 (Folder 12)
  - Hilda B. Roberts Scheduling Books and Calendars - 1951 to 1982 (Folder 13)
  - University of Washington Nursing 101/102: Intro to Prof Nursing - 1958 to 1960 (Folder 14)
- Oversized Materials, Series 5
  - Scrapbook. Rho Nu Scrapbook, 1957. (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook. Affiliate Student Nurses Orientation Scrapbook, Veterans Administration, Walla Walla - 1955 (Folder 2)
  - Construction documentation. Door Schedule, ICNE Building - 1978 (Folder 3)
  - Construction documentation. Room Finish Schedule, ICNE Building - 1978 (Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook. Rho Nu Scrapbook, 1947. (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Poster. "Save his life… and find your own. Be a nurse" - 1947 (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Independent Study Unit Packets - 1975 to 1976 (Box 76, Folder 1)
- Courses, Series 6
  - ICNE Independent Study Unit Packets - 1975 to 1976 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Independent Study Unit Packets - 1976 (1 of 2) (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Independent Study Unit Packets - 1976 (2 of 2) (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Exams - 1981 to 1985 (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Exams - 1986 (Folder 5)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Exams Nursing 406 - 1985 to 1986 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Exams - 1987 to 1990 (1 of 2) (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Exams - 1987 to 1990 (2 of 2) (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Packets - 1976 to 1977 (1 of 2) (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Packets - 1976 to 1977 (2 of 2) (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Packet Curriculum A - 1978 to 1979 (1 of 2) (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Packet Curriculum A - 1978 to 1979 (2 of 2) (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Packets - 1977 to 1978 (1 of 2) (Folder 5)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Packets - 1977 to 1978 (2 of 2) (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Packets - Fall 1979 (1 of 2) (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Packets - Fall 1979 (2 of 2) (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Packets Curriculum B - 1979 (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Packets, Winter Term - 1979 to 1980 (Folder 5)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Packets - Spring 1980 (1 of 2) (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Packets - Spring 1980 (2 of 2) (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Packets Curriculum A - Spring 1980 (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Packets Curriculum B - Spring 1980 (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Packets - Fall 1980 (1 of 2) (Folder 5)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Packets - Fall 1980 (2 of 2) (Folder 6)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Packets - Fall 1982 (1 of 2) (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Packets - Fall 1982 (2 of 2) (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Packets - Spring 1988 (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Packets - Fall 1988 (1 of 2) (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Packets - Fall 1988 (2 of 2) (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Packets - Spring 1989 (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Packets - Fall 1989 (1 of 2) (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Packets - Fall 1989 (2 of 2) (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Packets - Spring 1990 (1 of 2) (Folder 5)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Packets - Spring 1990 (2 of 2) (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Packets - Fall 1990 (1 of 2) (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Packets - Fall 1990 (2 of 2) (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Packets - Spring 1991 (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Student Packets - Fall 1991 (1 of 2) (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Student Packets - Fall 1991 (2 of 2) (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Student Packets - Spring 1992 (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Student Packets - Fall 1992 (1 of 2) (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Student Packets - Fall 1992 (2 of 2) (Folder 5)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Packets - Spring 1993 (1 of 2) (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Packets - Spring 1993 (2 of 2) (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Packets - Fall 1993 (1 of 2) (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Packets - Fall 1993 (2 of 2) (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Student Packets - Spring 1994 (Folder 5)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Packets - Fall 1994 (1 of 2) (Folder 6)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Packets - Fall 1994 (2 of 2) (Folder 7)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Student Packets - Spring 1995 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - ICNE Learning Resources Unit Student Packets - Spring 1996 (Folder 2)
  - ICNE Learning Resource Packets - Fall 1996 (1 of 2) (Folder 3)
  - ICNE Learning Resource Packets - Fall 1996 (2 of 2) (Folder 4)
  - ICNE Learning Resource Packets - Spring 1997 (Folder 5)
  - ICNE Learning Resource Packets - Fall 1997 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Home Economics 480 Diet Therapy - Spring 1975 (Folder 2)
  - Home Economics 480 Diet Therapy - Fall 1976 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 100: Introduction to Nursing - Fall 1952 to Spring 1953 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 100: Introduction to Nursing - Fall 1955 to Spring 1956 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 101: Introduction to Nursing - Fall 1955 to Spring 1956 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 101: Introduction to Nursing - Fall 1963 to Spring 1964 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 101: Introduction to Nursing - Fall 1964 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 101: Introduction to Nursing - Spring 1965 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 101: Introduction to Nursing - Fall 1965 to Spring 1966 (Folder 10)
  - Nursing 101: Introduction to Nursing - Fall 1966 to Spring 1967 (Folder 11)
  - Nursing 101: Introduction to Nursing - Fall 1967 to Spring 1968 (Folder 12)
  - Nursing 101: Introduction to Nursing - Fall 1968 to Spring 1969 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 101: Introduction to Nursing - Fall 1970 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 101: Introduction to Nursing - Spring 1971 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 101: Introduction to Nursing - Fall 1972 to Spring 1973 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 101: Introduction to Nursing - Fall 1973 to Spring 1974 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 102: Nursing 2 - Fall 1955 to Spring 1956 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 110: Introduction to Nursing and Related Professions - 1974 to 1977 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 110: Introduction to Nursing and Related Professions; Student Assignments and Course Evaluations - 1970s (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 121: Home Nursing and Community Health - 1962 to 1977 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 121: Home Nursing and Community Health, American Red Cross Materials (1 of 2) (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 121: Home Nursing and Community Health, American Red Cross Materials (2 of 2) (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 135: Generalized Public Health Nursing - 1939 to 1952 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 160: current Trends in Nursing - Fall 1953 to Spring 1954 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 200: Profession of Nursing - Fall 1987 to Spring 1988 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 200: Profession of Nursing - Fall 1988 to Spring 1989 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 200: Profession of Nursing - Fall 1989 to Spring 1990 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 200: Profession of Nursing - Fall 1990 to Spring 1991 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 200: Profession of Nursing - Fall 1991 to Spring 1992 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 200: Profession of Nursing - Fall 1992 to Spring 1993 (Folder 10)
  - Nursing 200: Profession of Nursing - Fall 1993 to Spring 1994 (Folder 11)
  - Nursing 200: Profession of Nursing - Fall 1994 to Spring 1995 (Folder 12)
  - Nursing 200: Profession of Nursing - Fall 1995 (Folder 13)
  - Nursing 200: Profession of Nursing - Spring 1996 (Folder 14)
  - Nursing 200: Profession of Nursing - Fall 1996 (Folder 15)
  - Nursing 200: Profession of Nursing - Spring 1997 (Folder 16)
  - Nursing 200: Profession of Nursing - Fall 1997 (Folder 17)
  - Nursing 201 - Fall 1956 to Spring 1957 (Folder 18)
  - Nursing 202: Profession of Nursing - Fall 1987 (Folder 19)
  - Nursing 250/251/252- Fall 1954 to Spring 1955 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 254: Pathology - Fall 1954 to Spring 1955 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 255: Professional Adjustments I - Fall 1954 to Spring 1958 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 256: Pharmacology and Therapeutics - Fall 1954 to Spring 1955 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 260: Medical Nursing - Fall 1954 to Spring 1955 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 261: Principles of Aseptic Nursing - Fall 1954 to Spring 1955 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 262: Medical Nursing Practice (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 263: Surgical Nursing Practice - Fall 1955 to Spring 1956 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 264: Principles of Diet Therapy - Fall 1954 to Spring 1955 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 265: Diet Practice (Folder 10)
  - Nursing 300: Basic Nursing - Summer 1969 (Folder 11)
  - Nursing 300: Basic Nursing - Fall 1969 to Spring 1970 (Folder 12)
  - Nursing 300: Basic Nursing - Summer 1970 (Folder 13)
  - Nursing 300: Basic Nursing - Fall 1970 (Folder 14)
  - Nursing 300: Basic Nursing - Summer 1971 (Folder 15)
  - Nursing 300: Basic Nursing - Fall 1971 to Spring 1972 (Folder 16)
  - Nursing 300: Basic Nursing - Summer 1972 (Folder 17)
  - Nursing 300: Basic Nursing - Fall 1973 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 300: Basic Nursing - Fall 1974 to Spring 1975 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 300: Basic Nursing - Fall 1975 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 300: Basic Nursing - Fall 1976 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 300: Basic Nursing - Fall 1977 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 300: Basic Nursing - Fall 1978 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 300: Basic Nursing, Miscellaneous Handouts - 1972 to 1980 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 300: History of Nursing, Course Materials - Fall 1953 to Spring 1954 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 300: History of Nursing - Fall 1954 to Spring 1955 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 300: History of Nursing Project, Correspondence of Chesta Hayden - 1948 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 300: History of Nursing Project "History of Anaesthesia" - 1948 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 300: History of Nursing Project "Indian Health Service" - 1946 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 300: History of Nursing Project "Look Before You Leap: Interviews with Nurses on Nursing" (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 300: History of Nursing Project "Missionary Nurse" - 1940s (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 300: History of Nursing Project "Nursing in Australia" (Folder 9)